# Franco Panozzo Vitoloni

# Front End Software Engineer

Phone - (+31) 6 29 44 49 29

Email - francopanozzo@hotmail.com.ar

#### **SUMMARY**

Enthusiastic self-taught web developer specialized in Frontend. I take pride in troubleshooting technical challenges while maintaining a keen focus on business objectives and strategic vision. My passion lies in crafting responsive and accessible web solutions that positively impact real users. Based in Spain and thriving in a remote work environment.

# **SKILLS AND TECH**

**Main skills:** Vue 2 and 3, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, SCSS, Tailwind, HTML, Nuxt, Vite, Vuex, Pinia, Node.js, Git, Docker, Figma.

**Past experience with:** React/Next/Redux, Adobe XD, Trello, Pug, SQL, Node/Express.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### TMC by Unilabs - Frontend Developer

Jul 2022 - Present

- Spearheading the future of radiology training for TMC Academy, focusing on online training for medical specialists.
- Designed and developed a responsive solution for an existing web app.
- Skills utilized: Microservices, Nuxt.js, Agile Methodologies, Vue.js, Tailwind CSS.

#### **K-LAGAN - Consultant**

Jul 2022 - Present

- Contributing expertise to technology and consulting projects at K-LAGAN.
- Skills utilized: Nuxt.js, Vue.js, Tailwind CSS.

# **Corsearch (Remote)** - Software Engineer

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022

- As part of the Oculist team: Implemented features related to machine learning image matching UI, for example: Image filters, imaging tab on listings, etc.
- As part of the Chieftain team: Implemented features related to rules and configurations related to web scraping and machine learning matching algorithms.
- Legal SaaS whose business model revolves around infringement recognition and enforcement.

# The Cirqle (Remote) - Front end developer

May 2021 - Jun 2022

- As part of a small engineering team migrating all the different SaaS apps the company offers to an unified web-app I worked mainly with the following tech stack (and the most important libraries): Nuxt, Vuex, Vue, Pug, SCSS, Element UI, Figma, Github, Asana, several REST APIs, Chart.js, moment, axios, gsap.
- Migrating old cirqle ui component library to a new design inside the project (
  It was deployed as an npm package before, which made it difficult for CI/CD)
- Migrating Bootstrap utility classes (mainly) to use our own design system and Element UI theming.
- Creation of multiple pages and components, some of the more complex ones included graphs and tables with loads of dynamic data and CRUD interactivity.
- Ownership of the Influencers UI, used by influencers to work with our team and corporate clients.
- Agile methodology with daily standups and bi-weekly demo and standown meetings to share our progress with the rest of the company and reflect ourselves on the improvements needed.

# **Zetenta.com** - Front end web developer

Jan 2021 - May 2021

- Wrote fully responsive websites based on designs. Deadlines were always met while maintaining high standards for performance, UX/UI and code readability.
- Redesign of custom Wordpress themes for small companies such as real estate agencies and shopping malls.
- Developed a SPA using Vanilla JS, to show the work of MSF on pandemics.
- Integration of a Wordpress theme with a 3rd party real estate CMS (Tokko)

 Integrated 3rd party software solutions and libraries such as: jVectorMap, Swiper.js, Google Map API, YouTube API, Facebook, Instagram and Twitter share APIs, etc.

# **EDUCATION**

**Treehouse** - Front End Web Development Track

Mar 2020 - Aug 2020

Followed a web development online course on front end development from beginner to knowing all the basics and some more. I learned most of the technologies and methodologies I now use after this on my own, be it via youtube, paid video courses or reading the documentation, books or blogs.

Universidad de El Salvador, Buenos Aires, ARG - Medicine

Jul 2016 - Mar 2018

Successfully completed pre-med school and got into Medicine. After completing my first year I decided to move abroad and pursue other interests.

# **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish Native
- English C1 (Proficient)
- French C1 (Proficient)